RG 062:133, Town of Sprague
Connecticut State Library
Town of Sprague records
1861-1939
Connecticut State Library
Sprague (Conn.)
13 cubic feet
Administrative, school and tax records for the town of Sprague.
RG062_133
T000975
Historical Note
The town of Sprague was incorporated in May 1861 and was taken from Lisbon and Franklin.
Scope and Content
Administrative, school and tax records for the town of Sprague.
Index Terms
Subjects:
School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Sprague -- Statistics; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Sprague -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Sprague -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Sprague -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Sprague -- Registers
Places:
Sprague (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1861-1939
  - School registers, 1902, 1917-1938 (Box Boxes 1-4)
  - Board of Education files, includes correspondence, bills, receipts, lists of teachers, enumerations, lists of students, other financial records, 1926-1939; in accordian files (Box Boxes 5-11)
  - Board of Education orders and accounts, 1926-1933 (Box Boxes 12-13)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1914-1919 are not boxed.
    - 1861, 1861-1862, 1863-1864, 1865, 1866, 1867-1868, 1869-1870 (Box Box 14)
      The 1861 volume is for the First School District.
    - 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 15)
    - 1880, 1881-1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886 (Box Box 16)
    - 1887, 1888, 1889-1890, 1891, 1892-1893, 1894 (Box Box 17)
    - 1895-1896, 1897, 1898, 1899-1903, 1904-1907 (Box Box 18)
    - 1908-1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913 (Box Box 19)
    - 1914, 1 volume
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume